All Your Files Has Been Encrypted

You Have to Pay to Get Your Files Back

You cannot decrypt the files yourself. This will only corrupt the files

The only way to decrypt is to purchase a unique private key from us

Only we can give you this key and only we can recover your files

1-Go to C:\ProgramData\ or in Your  Drives and send us key.Cortizol key file

2-To be sure we have the decryptor and it works you can send an email: cortizol@atomicmail.io and decrypt one file for free.
But this file should be of not valuable!

3-Changing Windows without saving KEY.Cortizol file will cause permanent Data loss

Do you want to restore your files?
Write to email: cortizol@atomicmail.io
Or send me a message on Telegram. My ID: https://t.me/Cortizol2025

ID: id-0000000000

Attention!
 * Do not rename encrypted files.
 * Do not try to decrypt your data using third party software, it may cause permanent data loss.
